biggboss10.me 2018-08-27

# Privacy Policy - Bigg Boss 12

**Personally Provided Information**  
You do not have to give us personal information to visit BiggBoss12. If you choose to provide us with additional information through an e-mail message, inquiry form, comments, etc., we will only maintain the information as long as needed to respond to your question, inquiry, or to fulfill the stated purpose of the communication. Except for authorized law enforcement investigations, we do not give, share, sell or transfer any personal information to a third party.

**External Links**  
Our web site may contain links to other sites. BiggBoss12 is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each web site to which we may link that may collect personal information.

We DO NOT host any videos on this website. All videos found on our site are found freely available around the web on sites such as Daily Motion, Tune Etc. We make no guarantees or promises in our service and take no liability for our users actions. We are not affiliated nor claim to be affiliated with any of the owners of videos/streams played on our site. All content is copyright of their respective owners.

**Website Traffic Analysis Software**  
For site security purposes and to ensure that this service remains available to all users, we employ software programs to monitor traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage. We also monitor our traffic to analyze visitors’s information, such as, but not limited to, operating system, browsers, screen resolutions and similar.

In the event of authorized law enforcement investigations, and pursuant to any required legal process, information from these sources may be used to help identify an individual.

**Advertisers**  
We use outside ad companies to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies and are collected by the ad companies, and we do not have access to this information. We work with the ad company: Google Adsense. Please check their websites for respective privacy policies.  
Please note that we strictly do not allow competitive advertisements.
